Guide to the Lost Roads Publishers Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Lost Roads Publishers records
1980-2006
YCAL MSS 726
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
21.42
(25 boxes)
The Lost Roads Publishers Records provide insight into the activities of an independent American press operating in the late twentieth-century. The records include correspondence, writings, audiovisual media, and electronic files relating to Lost Roads Publishers and its authors.
Lost Roads Publishers
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Forrest Gander and C.D. Wright, 2007 and purchased from C.D. Wright on the Alfred Z. Baker, Jr. Fund, 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 20, 21, and 25 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 23 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Lost Roads Publishers
Lost Roads Publishers is an independent literary publisher that produces books of poetry, literary fiction, and translation by emerging and well-known writers. Frank Stanford founded Lost Roads Publishers in Arkansas in 1976. Following Stanford's death in 1978, C.D. Wright and Forrest Gander assumed editorship and moved the press to Rhode Island. Now known as the Lost Roads Press, the company is currently based in Wyoming where Susan Scarlata serves as the senior editor.
Scope and Contents
The Lost Roads Publishers Records provide insight into the activities of an independent American press operating in the late twentieth-century. The records include correspondence, writings, audiovisual media, and electronic files relating to Lost Roads Publishers and its authors.
Arrangement
Organized into two groupings: I. January 2007 Acquisition. II. October 2012 Acquisition.
Publishers and publishing; Audiocassettes -- United States -- 20th Century; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 20th Century; Born digital -- United States -- 20th Century; Electronic documents -- United States -- 20th Century; Videocassettes -- United States -- 20th Century; Gander, Forrest, 1956-; Stanford, Frank, 1949-1978; Wright, C. D., 1949-2016; Lost Roads Publishers
- I. January 2007 Acquisition, 20.25; (23 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Contains: correspondence, writings, audiovisual material, and electronic files relating to Lost Roads Publishers.
  Boxes 20 and 21 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 23 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 938
  - Correspondence and Manuscripts
    - Adamo, Ralph, Sadness at the Private University, Lost Roads #3 (Box 1)
    - Adamo, Ralph, The End of the World, printed version, Lost Roads #17 (Box 1)
    - Adamo, Ralph, correspondence, 2 (Box 1)
    - Adamo, Ralph, The End of the World, Manuscript (Box 1)
    - Adamo, Ralph, memorabilia (Box 1)
    - Adamo, Ralph, Sadness at the Private University, manuscript (Box 1)
    - Benitez, Zuleyka, memorabilia (Box 1)
    - Benitez, Zuleyka, correspondence (Box 1)
    - Benitez, Zuleyka (Box 1)
    - ["B" Divider] (Box 1)
    - Benitez, Zuleyka, manuscript (Box 1)
    - Broughton, Irv, correspondence (Box 1)
    - Broughton, Irv (Box 1)
    - Bundy, Alison (Box 1)
    - Bundy, Alison, A Bad Business, printed version, Lost Roads #27 (Box 1)
    - Bundy, Alison, correspondence, various papers (Box 1)
    - Bundy, Alison, A Bad Business, manuscript (Box 1)
    - Bundy, Alison and Mary Caponegro, promotion and distribution material (Box 1)
    - Caldwell, Justin (Box 1)
    - Caldwell, Justin, The Sleeping Porch, printed version, Lost Roads #16 (Box 1)
    - Caldwell, Justin, correspondence (Box 1)
    - Caldwell, Justin, The Sleeping Porch, manuscripts (Box 1)
    - Caldwell, Justin, memorabilia (Box 1)
    - ["F Divider], [Empty Folder] (Box 1)
    - Caponegro, Mary, manuscript (Box 1)
    - Caponegro, Mary, correspondence re: printing (Box 1)
    - Caponegro, Mary, memorabilia (Box 1)
    - Char, Rene ["N" Divider] (Box 1)
    - Char, Rene, No Siege is Absolute, printed version, Lost Roads #24 tr. Wright (Box 1)
    - Char, Rene - Wright, C.D., correspondence (Box 1)
    - Wright - Franz, correspondence not re: CHAR, 3 (Box 2)
    - Wright - Franz, correspondence, 3 (Box 2)
    - Char - Wright, manuscript, 2 (Box 2)
    - Craver, Mark, 2 (Box 2)
    - Craver, Mark, The Problem of Grace, copy of thesis (Box 2)
    - Craver, Mark, The Problem of Grace, book (Box 2)
    - Craver, Mark, manuscript (Box 2)
    - Craver, Mark, Story: More and Better Water (Box 2)
    - Craver, Mark, correspondence (Box 2)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, El Nino, final galleys (Box 2)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, El Nino, manuscript (Box 2)
    - ["H" Divider] (Box 3)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, El Nino, book (Box 3)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, El Nino, cover (Box 3)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, El Nino, dummy for setter (Box 3)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, El Nino, correspondence, 3 (Box 3)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, El Nino, typesetting (Box 4)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, correspondence (Not Lost Roads) (Box 4)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, Hard Country, manuscript (Box 4)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, Psyche Drives the Coast, manuscript (Box 4)
    - "K" [File Divider] (Box 4)
    - Duval, Quinton, Dinner Music, printed version, Lost Roads #20 (Box 4)
    - Duval, Quinton, correspondence (Box 4)
    - Duval, Quinton, Dinner Music, manuscript (Box 4)
    - Duval, Quinton, manuscript, printed version (Box 4)
    - ["Foss. Philip" Divider] (Box 4)
    - Foss, Philip, The Composition of Glass (Box 4)
    - Foss, Philip, correspondence (Box 4)
    - Foss, Philip, galleys (Box 4)
    - Foss, Philip, The Composition of Glass, manuscript (Box 4)
    - Foss, Philip, The Excuses of the Capricas, manuscript (Box 4)
    - Foss, Philip, typescripts, communication with typesetters (Box 4)
    - Gilchrist, Ellen, manuscript (Box 4)
    - Gilchrist, Ellen, correspondence (Box 4)
    - Heller, Barbara, New Orleans, my darling, photos/negatives (Box 4)
    - Heller, Barbara, New Orleans, my darling, manuscript (Box 4)
    - Heller, Barbara, Wright, C. D., New Orleans, my darling, edited manuscript (Box 4)
    - Heller, Barbara, Wright, C. D., New Orleans, my darling, typeset text (Box 4)
    - Heller, Barbara, New Orleans, my darling (Box 4)
    - Heller, Barbara, New Orleans, my darling (Box 5)
    - ["T" Divider] (Box 5)
    - Howe, Fanny, The Vineyard (Box 5)
    - Howe, Fanny, correspondence (Box 5)
    - Howe, Fanny, galleys (Box 5)
    - Howe, Fanny, manuscript (Box 5)
    - Howe, Fanny, typescript, 2 (Box 5)
    - ["J" Divider"] (Box 5)
    - Johnson, Honor, production papers and correspondence (Box 5)
    - Johnson, Honor, manuscript (Box 5)
    - Mayes, Francis, Hours, 2 (Box 5)
    - Mayes, Francis, Hours (Box 5)
    - Mayes, Francis, Hours, manuscript, 2 (Box 5)
    - Mayes, Francis, Hours, mailing list (Box 5)
    - Mayes, Francis, correspondence, 2 (Box 5)
    - McKernan, John, Walking Along the Missouri River (Box 6)
    - McKernan, John, Walking Along the Missouri River, manuscript (Box 6)
    - McKernan, John, correspondence (Box 6)
    - Morris, John S., Bean Street (Box 6)
    - Morris, John S., Bean Street, manuscript (Box 6)
    - Morris, John S., correspondence (Box 6)
    - Rice, Stan, Body of Work, 2 (Box 6)
    - ["S" Divider] (Box 6)
    - Sklarew, Myra, correspondence (Box 6)
    - Sklarew, Myra, production (Box 6)
    - Sklarew, Myra, manuscript, 2 (Box 6)
    - Schmidt, Paulette; Soupault, Philippe (Box 6)
    - Schmidt, Paulette; Soupault, Philippe, manuscript (Box 6)
    - Stern, Steve, Metamorphosis (Box 6)
    - Stern, Steve, Isaac and the Undertaker's Daughter, 2 (Box 6)
    - Schmidt, Paulette; Soupault, Philippe, correspondence (Box 6)
    - Stein, correspondence, 2 (Box 6)
    - Stoss, John, Finding the Broom (Box 6)
    - Schmidt, Paulette; Soupault, Philippe, manuscript (Box 7)
    - Wright, C.D., Terrorism (Box 7)
    - Waldrop, Keith, galleys (Box 7)
    - Stoss, John (Box 7)
    - Sze, Arthur / Maclow (Box 7)
    - Sze, Arthur, correspondence (Box 7)
    - Sze, Arthur, River River (Box 7)
    - Sze, Arthur, 2 (Box 7)
    - Waldrop Keith [Divider] (Box 7)
    - Wright, C.D., Terrorism (Box 7)
    - Waldrop, Keith, manuscript, 3 (Box 7)
    - Waldrop, Keith, typesetting, 2 (Box 7)
    - Waldrop, Keith, corrected galleys (Box 7)
    - Waldrop, Keith, grants (Box 7)
    - Whitlow, Carolyn Beard (Box 7)
    - Whitlow, Carolyn Beard, manuscript (Box 7)
    - Whitlow, Carolyn Beard, graphics (Box 7)
    - Wright, C.D., Terrorism (Box 7)
    - Wright, C.D., Room Rented by a Single Woman (Box 7)
    - Wright, C.D., manuscript (Box 7)
    - Wright, C.D., various papers (Box 7)
  - Business Papers
    - Copyright Info (Box 8)
    - Banking (Box 8)
    - LRP miscellaneous for file (Box 8)
    - [Bank mail], 3 (Box 8)
    - [Invoices], 2 (Box 8)
    - Unpaid/unreimbursed [invoices] (Box 8)
    - Jobbers [invoices] (Box 8)
    - Returns and Complications (Box 8)
    - Old and Unpaid (Box 8)
    - Unpaid Authors Invoices (Box 8)
    - Returned Checks (Box 8)
    - Invoices Unpaid (Box 8)
    - NEA Grants (Box 8)
    - NEA 1992-93 (Box 8)
    - NEA 1991 (Box 8)
    - [NEA unlabeled] (Box 8)
    - NEA 1987 (Box 8)
    - National Foundation for the Arts, correspondence (Box 9)
    - RISCA, Tender Buttons (Box 9)
    - RISCA Grants (Box 9)
    - RISCA Grants, A Bad Business, Tales From the Next Village (Box 9)
    - RISCA, Wild Meat (Box 9)
    - RISCA, catalog 87 (Box 9)
    - RISCA/Waldrop Grant (Box 9)
    - N.E. Foundation for Arts Grant (Box 9)
    - Lost Roads Stationary (Box 9)
    - Waldrop/Taggart (Box 9)
    - Brathwaite, Kamau (Box 9)
    - [Flyers for Endou] (Box 9)
    - Mayes (Box 9)
    - Old titles (Box 9)
    - [LRP Pamphlets] (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 9)
    - [Book flyers] (Box 9)
    - Books out of print (Box 9)
    - Soliciting & Berger (Box 9)
    - Conditions Uncertain (Box 9)
    - They Come for What You Love (Box 9)
    - The Desire Notebooks (Box 9)
    - Review copy file (Box 9)
    - Addresses etc. (Box 9)
    - Peer Reviews (Box 9)
    - Jacobs Material (Box 9)
    - Libraries (Box 9)
    - Truitt public relations (Box 9)
    - Jacobs manuscript (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 9)
    - Library of Congress and Copyright Claims (Box 9)
  - Manuscripts A-W
    - "A"
      - [Adamo, Ralph] (Box 10)
    - "B"
      - [Bellen, Martine] (Box 10)
    - "C"
      - [Berssenbrugge, Mei-mei] (Box 10)
      - [Howe, Fanny] (Box 10)
      - [Brown, Lee Ann] (Box 10)
      - [Cole, Peter], 2 (Box 10)
      - [Claudel, Paul] (Box 10)
      - [Cole, Peter], 2 (Box 10)
    - "D"
      - [Miscellaneous papers] (Box 10)
      - Ducornet (Box 10)
    - "E"
      - Charles Hartman (Box 10)
    - "F"
      - [Fraser, Kathleen] (Box 10)
    - "G"
      - Peter Gizzi (Box 10)
      - [Godfrey, John] (Box 10)
      - [Gurnis?] (Box 10)
      - Hartman - Downfall of the Straight Line (Box 10)
      - Richard Howard [postcards] (Box 10)
    - "I" (Box 10)
      - [Iskrenko, Nina] (Box 10)
    - "K"
      - [Keineg, Poul] (Box 10)
      - [Kleinschmidt, Edward], 4 (Box 10)
    - "M"
      - Mayes [Talking Back], 2 (Box 11)
      - Milligan, Marjorie (Box 11)
    - "R"
      - Ratcliffe - Spaces in the Light (Box 11)
      - [Rehm, Pamela Sue] (Box 11)
    - "S"
      - Sze, Arthur, Archipelago (Box 11)
      - [Swenson, Cole - Animism] (Box 11)
      - [Swenson, Cole - Span] (Box 11)
      - [ poetry] (Box 11)
      - [Swensen, Cole - Oar] (Box 11)
      - [Sato, Hiroaki] (Box 11)
    - "T"
      - [Tejada, Roberto] (Box 11)
    - "W" (Box 11)
      - [Weinberger - World Beat], 2 (Box 11)
      - [Waldrop, Rosemarie] (Box 11)
      - [Eliz Willis] (Box 11)
      - Weiners (Box 11)
      - Wiegl - The Hand That Takes (Box 11)
  - Manuscripts, proofs, correspondence
    - Foo, Josephine (Box 12)
    - Foo, Josephine (Box 12)
    - Foo, Josephine, manuscript (Box 12)
    - Foo, Josephine, manuscripts, proofs, 2 (Box 12)
    - Foo, Josephine, Karl Barx (Box 12)
    - Brathwaite, Kamau, Trench Town Rock (Box 12)
    - Jacobs, J. L., The Leaves in Her Shoes (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous manuscript and proofs, 2 (Box 12)
    - Taggart, John, Standing Wave (Box 12)
    - [Mayes - Ex Voto] (Box 12)
    - Taggart, John, Standing Wave (Box 12)
    - Taggart, John, Extra published poems (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 12)
  - Business papers, publicity, clippings
    - Website LRP (Box 13)
    - Ads (Box 13)
    - Lost Roads Ads - Actual Ads (Box 13)
    - Xeroxes of Ads; Copies (Box 13)
    - Book Fairs (Box 13)
    - Distribution Matters (Box 13)
    - Catalog production (Box 13)
    - Lost Roads Publishers Catalog (Box 13)
    - Catalog (Box 13)
    - Catalog production (Box 13)
    - Catalogue: 1980 (Box 13)
    - [miscellaneous papers] (Box 13)
    - [Divider] (Box 13)
  - Manuscripts, business papers, correspondence
    - Letters about Lost Roads authors (Box 14)
    - Broadsides [correspondence] (Box 14)
    - Queries, submissions 91-92 (Box 14)
    - Sample Queries 88-90-91 (Box 14)
    - Sample queries 85-87 (Box 14)
    - Selected Queries 1984 (Box 14)
    - Jim Hartz [correspondence] (Box 14)
    - Cuddihy, Michael, Ironwood (Box 14)
    - [miscellaneous correspondence] (Box 14)
    - Weigl, Bruce, correspondence (Box 14)
    - [IRS] (Box 14)
    - NEA Grant 1977 (Box 14)
    - NEA 1978-80 (Box 14)
    - Bookstore Info -- Palo Alto Printers, Inc. (Box 14)
    - Early Lost Roads nonprofit status/copyright (Box 14)
    - State taxes (Box 14)
    - Old corp/nonprofit/IRS/business (Box 14)
    - Bellen, Martine, Poems from a Height (Box 14)
    - Boullosa, Carmen, manuscript (Box 14)
    - Brown, Lee Ann (Box 14)
    - Cuddity, manuscript (Box 14)
    - Culhane, Three Love Songs (Box 14)
    - Forche, Carolyn, The Angel of History (Box 14)
    - Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 14)
    - Gilbert, manuscript (Box 14)
    - Gizzi, Peter (Box 14)
    - Klappert, Peter, manuscript (Box 14)
    - Mayes, How Bright Are All Things Here (Box 14)
    - [McMorris] (Box 14)
    - Milligan, Marjorie (Box 14)
    - Stern, Steve, Hyman the Magnificent (Box 14)
  - Galleys, proofs, manuscripts
    Includes correspondence, graphics, photographs and slides
    - Brathwaite, Kamau, 2 (Box 15)
    - [empty folder] (Box 15)
    - French Town Rock, proofs, 2 (Box 15)
    - Berger, Donald, 9 (Box 15)
    - Jacobs, J. L., The Leaves in Her Shoes, 3 (Box 15)
    - Truitt, Sam, Anamorphosis Eisenhower, 7 (Box 15)
    - Truitt, Sam, Anamorphosis Eisenhower, 2 (Box 16)
    - Berger, Donald, 2 (Box 16)
    - Swenson, Doug (Box 16)
    - Waldrop, Keith, 3 (Box 16)
    - White, Edmund, 7 (Box 16)
    - Banking (Box 16)
    - Review copy form letter (Box 16)
    - Remittence form letter (Box 16)
    - Form letters (Box 16)
    - Post office (Box 16)
    - Authors newsletter (Box 16)
    - Editorial assistant (Box 16)
    - ellaneous correspondence (Box 16)
    - Printers (Box 16)
    - Unfiled receipts (Box 16)
    - Invoices (Box 17)
    - Permissions (Box 17)
    - Individual authors (Box 17)
    - Lost Roads/Brown (Box 17)
    - Brown receipts (Box 17)
    - Paid orders from individuals (Box 17)
    - Segue Foundation, correspondence (Box 17)
    - Independent literary magazines (Box 17)
    - University of Arkansas, royalties (Box 17)
    - Writer's Center, contracts (Box 17)
    - Small presses (Box 17)
    - Credit file (Box 17)
    - Confield [photos, corresondence] (Box 17)
    - Chestnutt, Vic (Box 17)
    - Docorney, Guy (Box 17)
    - De Leo, Hank (Box 17)
    - Slides (Box 17)
    - Foo, Josephine (Box 17)
    - Grace Rubbinjs (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 17)
    - May An Hayden (Box 17)
    - Imamura, photographs, slides, 2 (Box 17)
    - Images, mixed (Box 17)
    - Johnson, Richard, slides, 2 (Box 17)
    - Kennedy, Kevin, 2 (Box 17)
    - Luster, Deborah, 2 (Box 17)
    - Mixed photos (Box 18)
    - Moers, Denny (Box 18)
    - Denny's show (Box 18)
    - Smith, H. Lane (Box 18)
    - Stanford, Ginny (Box 18)
    - Photos/negatives (Box 18)
    - Duvernet slides (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 18)
    - Covers (Box 18)
    - Lined image (Box 18)
    - Authors and staff, photographs (Box 18)
    - Logo (Box 18)
    - Essays (Box 18)
    - The Woman Who Loved Blue Duck (Box 18)
    - Cooling Time, 4 (Box 18)
    - Cooling Time, 3 (Box 19)
    - "Of the Malsery," essay (Box 19)
    - Gulf War essay (Box 19)
    - Stein essay (Box 19)
    - The Passenger (Box 19)
    - Eye of the Line (Box 19)
    - Battlefield (Box 19)
    - Rough cuts (Box 19)
    - "Essay on mothering" (Box 19)
    - Hoerman (Box 19)
    - Keineg, Paol (Box 19)
    - "Come shining" (Box 19)
    - Essays, 3 (Box 19)
    - Lost Roads project, printed version, 2 copies (Box 19)
    - Guest book (Box 19)
    - Notebook (Box 19)
    - Invitations to book reception (Box 19)
  - Audiovisual Material
    Conditions Governing Access
    Boxes 20-21 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Audiocassettes, (22 audiocassettes)
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Lost Roads - Writers 10-16; c. Dragonwagon starts again on side 2, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615100)
      - Sister Rosetta Tharpe; Sonny Boy Williamson (Rice Miller), King Biscuit Time, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615092)
      - Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Le Hot Club De France, 1992
        This is a commerical audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
      - The Cruel Animal, Terry Wright, 1993; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615118)
        A list of contents is included with this audiocassette.
        Garbage In (Radio Excerpt)
        The Juicy Life
        Nothing On
        Seven Sins (Excerpts)
        Undeclared Love Triangle
        Fun and No Fun (Excerpts)
        Halloween
        Play Rehearsal
        Atrium
        Portrait
        The Gestapo Predicts
        The Reagan Years (Excerpts)
        Hailing Metal
        Plutonium
        Recording (Excerpts)
        Garbage In (Live Excerpt)
      - Lost Roads Project, Tape 2 - Finished Productions, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615126)
      - Robert Titus (Whitefeather), Helena, AR; Robert Cochran (Vance Randolph), Fayetteville, AR, 1993 October 13; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615134)
      - The Lost Roads Project, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615142)
        Included are: Donald Harrington, Jo McDougal, Dee Brown, Vance Rudolph, Margaret Bolsterli, Crescent Dragonwagon, Pat Phillips, Henry Dumas, and Jim Whitehead
      - All Things Considered, "Poetry of the Ozarks", 1995 July 26; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615159)
      - Lost Roads Walk In Book (R. Johnson) - 2 pieces, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615167)
      - Jimmy Driftwood, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615175)
        Battle of New Orleans
        Rattlesnake Song
        Sailor Man
        Shanty in the Hollow
        Unfortunate Man
        Long Chain
        Tennessee Stud
        Soldier's Joy
        The Giant on the Thunderhead
        Mooshantanio
        Old Joe Clark
        Wilderness Road
        Down in the Arkansas
        The Timbercutter's Song
        The Courtin Song
        Ozark Bill
        On the Banks of the Buffalo
        Beautiful White River Valley
        In the Ouachita Mtns.
        The Horsetrader's Song
        Bows & Arrows; Arrows & Bows
        The Ballad of Jim Barry
        That's the Way They Do in Arkansas
        In a Mountain Village
      - The Lost Roads Project - Tape 1a and 1b, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615183)
        Included are: Sonny Boy Williamson, Lily Peter, Frank Stanford, Shirley Abbot, C. Van[n] Woodward, Besimilr Brigham, Andrea Budy, Jack Butler, and Miller Williams
      - Lost Roads: Jim Whitehead, 7:34, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615191)
      - Lost Roads Project, Tape 1, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615209)
      - The Lost Roads Project, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615217)
        Included: Sonny Boy Williamson, Lily Peter, Frank Sanford, Shirley Abbot, C. Vann Woodward, Besmilr Brigham, Andrea Budy, Jack Butler, and Miller Williams
      - Adella Hale; Houston Stackhouse, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615225)
      - Crescent Dragonwagon, pt. 1; Crescent Dragonwagon, pt. 2, Jo McDougal, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615233)
      - The Lost Roads Project, tapes 2a and 2b, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615241)
        Included: Donald Harrington, Jo McDougal, Dee Brown, Vance Randolph, Margaret Bolsteri, Crescent Dragonwagon, Pat Phillips, Henry Dumas, and Jim Whitehead
      - The Lost Roads Project: Walk-in Book of Arkansas - 2 pieces, soundtrack: Richard Johnson, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615258)
      - Lost Roads - finished segments (10), undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615266)
      - Lost Roads - 10 Interviews, Rough Edits, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615274)
      - Lost Roads: One Each, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615282)
        Frank Stanford, "Circle of Lorca"
        Besmilr Brigham, "The Willis Lore"
        Dee Brown from "Bury My Heart"
        Jim Whitehead, "Forecast"
        Andrea Budy, "Black"
        Carrie Jamison, "The Shadow of Choice"
        Donald Harington from "Architecture"
        Jo McDougal, "The Shrimp"
        Sonny Boy Williamson, "Bye Sight to the Blind"
        Margaret Bolsterli from "Born in the Delta"
        Lily Peter from "The Great Ridge"
        Vance Randolph from "Healing"
        Crescent Dragonwagon, "Skillet Sizzled in Milk Cornbread"
        Henry Dumas, "A Mad Dog Will Bite Anybody"
        Miller Williams, "Pulling Back"
        Jack Butler from "Living in [Little] Rock/[Miss Little Rock]
      - Sunday Showcase Concert, University of Arkansas, 1996 October 27; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104615290)
        A list of contents is included with this digital audiotape.
        "What about this" - Frank Stanford
        De Profundis - Robert Mueller
        Four Miniatures for Woodwind Quintet - Philip Parker
        Studies for Player Piano, vol. IV, No. 21 - Conlon Nancarrow
        Songs of Separation - William Grant Still
        "Goodbye Sweetwater" - Henry Dumas
        Nocturne for Bass Trombone and Tape - James Greeson
        Prelude and Processional - John Turner
        Infinite Vista, Piano Fantasy - Dale Millen
        Cat concerto - Scott Bradley
    - Video Recordings (Box 21)
      - "Lost Roads", undated; YCALMSS726_0001; 1; 00:59:59 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002102301471)
      - "Dub" [Lost Roads?], undated; YCALMSS726_0002; 1; 00:52:00 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002102301489)
      - "Lost Roads By Heart #1", 1993 July; YCALMSS726_0003; 1; 00:59:59 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002102301497)
        1) Pine Bluff/UAR East Bay Gangstas 7/13/93 2)Poetry Night at Magees Hot Springs 7/14/93
      - "Lost Roads By Heart #2", 1993 July; YCALMSS726_0004; 1; 00:39:35 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002102301505)
        Bessmilr Brishem 7/18/93 Andrea Budy 7/19/93
      - "Lost Roads By Heart #3", 1993 July; YCALMSS726_0005; 1; 00:38:30; There is a blue screen at the beginning of the file for about a minute. (Box 21, Item barcode 39002102301513)
        Bill Willett 7/20/93 Judge Ernie Wright 7/21/93
      - "Lost Roads By Heart #4", 1993 July; YCALMSS726_0006; 1; 00:37:20 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002102301521)